Gamm, Sara Collection of Miscellaneous Materials from the New York City Transit Authority 5026
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sara Gamm Collection of Miscellaneous Materials from the New York City Transit Authority
1969-1970
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Gamm, Sara
New York City Transit Authority
5026
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Collective bargaining agreements, pamphlets, constitutions.
This collection consists of collective bargaining agreements between the New York City Transit Authority and a number of employee organizations, including supervisory organizations, rules and regulations (technical operating rules as well as regulations concerning leave and vacations), and other material relative to the personnel and labor relations aspects of the Transit Authority.
5513190
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 22, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, January 20, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Local transit -- Employees -- New York (State) -- New York; Local transit -- Management -- New York (State) -- New York; Collective labor agreements -- Transport workers -- New York (State) -- New York; New York (N.Y.)
5513190
- Agreement between NYC Transit Authority and Subway supervisors Association, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Agreement between NYC Transit Authority and AFL-CIO Division 1056, 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Agreement between NYC Transit Authority and Local 100, AFL-CIO, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Agreement between NYC Transit Authority and AFL-CIO 726, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Agreement between NYC Transit Authority and Queens Supervisory Association, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Agreement between NYC Transit Authority and Transit Supervisors Organization, 1964-1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- NYC Transit Authority Rules and Regulations (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Rules and Regulations Ch. 16 Vacation, Sick Leave, Other Allowances, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- NYC Transit Authority Schedule of Working Conditions for Employees in: Power, Maintenance of way, Bus Maintenance, Station, Railroad Watchman, Conductor, Motormen, 1961-1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Constitution of AFSCME, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Constitution of the Association of Western Pulp and Paper Workers, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)